[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Is there any indication at the moment about any motive for what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "You know, when you talk to people here, and this sounds like cliche, but it is so true with everyone that I've spoken to that knows this young man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Yes, do the -- do the Bobbies carry guns now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Very few.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What's your sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, I don't think they believe it as passionately as the right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Are you disappointed that Obama hasn't done something more concrete about guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What made you get up one day and say I'm going to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How bad are you going to miss it, Bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I'm driving a cab at night now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Have you heard from the president since your donation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, no, because it wasn't to him, it was to the super PAC.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Is it a silly argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "It's a silly argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "That's still hypocrisy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, first of all, he would just -- he would out-and-out lose this election if he didn't -- .", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Even if you think it's morally and ethically wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "But given that Romney is out-spending all his competitors with these super PACs, and like 10-1 and he still isn't getting very far, certainly winning his election battle at the moment, what makes you think the super PACs are actually that effective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Well, that's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Of course, every -- they always have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What would we think of a coach who didn't do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "He was crazy is what we would think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "It's true, when Rick -- when Rick Santorum says, you know, Obama thinks that your -- I don't know what -- what did he say about Obama that he wants to rule over you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "But here's the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick", "Rick Santorum", "Obama", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "How dare you say you won't be taking your orders from the Pope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I don't think he read the speech properly because that's not what Kennedy was saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What do you think of that whole argument on both sides?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "It's similar to the silly thing about you -- the designated hitter and how that's a hypocrite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "How much should the government lead, and how much strays into nanny state, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, sometimes you do need a nanny state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "If you were president, what are the three quick things that you would strive to do to put America back on its feet, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, first, I would invest.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Did you find that funny or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I hadn't seen that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "What's to get upset about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Do you like him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Why can't he do it with his religion, if he believes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, he can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "And actually, I suspect, do believe that it's perfectly acceptable for people of religious influence to work in politics as well and govern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "It is, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "If Jeremy Lin came to you and said, look, I want you to join me in prayer and I will score 20 more points against the Lakers, would you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy Lin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Would you simply have wanted -- not wanted, but have drawn the conclusion the only ethical or moral solution would be that the mother should die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "No one -- Piers, I love the way people who are pro-choice find the most grotesque possible moral dilemma to set up one side or her to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Where do you think life begins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I think it begins at conception.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "How do you plead to that charge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Well, I guess I'll use the word guilty, or very, very happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]